{
    "questions": [
        {
            "id" : "0",
            
            "question" :  "Where do I enjoy the room's attention being casted on?",

            
            "leftAnswer": "I enjoy being the center of attention"
            ,
            "rightAnswer": "I enjoy watching the spotlight casted onto someone else"
       
            
            
        
        },
        {
            "id" : "1",

            "question" : "How often am I on my phone?",
            
            "leftAnswer": "I only use it to text"
            ,
            "rightAnswer": "I'm scrolling for hours"
            
        },
        {
            "id" : "2",

            "question" : "How do I view exercise?"",
            "leftAnswer":  "I exercise frequently and take fitness seriously"
            ,
            "rightAnswer": "It is not important"
        },
        {
            "id" : "3",

            "question" : "How do I handle conflict?",
            "leftAnswer": "I try to avoid conflict"
            ,
            "rightAnswer": "I confront conflict head on despite it being uncomfortable"
        },
        {
            "id" : "4",

            "question" : "How do I recharge my battery?",
            "leftAnswer":  "I recharge best when I am alone"
            ,
            "rightAnswer": "I recharge best when I am with other people"
            
        },
        {
            "id" : "5",

            "question" : "How do I hold onto resentment?",
            "leftAnswer":  "I forgive immediately"
            ,
            "rightAnswer":"I can hold a grudge until I die"
        },
        {
            "id" : "6",

            "question" : "How do I view other people's opinions",
            "leftAnswer":"I am an open book"
            ,
            "rightAnswer":"I am a locked safe"
        },
        {
            "id" : "7",

            "question" : "How do I go throughout my day?",
            "leftAnswer":"I follow a strict schedule"
            ,
            "rightAnswer":"I go with the flow and do whatever pops up"
            
        },
        {
            "id" : "8",

            "question" : "How do I view the idea of people being imprisoned as a form of punishment?",
            "leftAnswer": "It is inhumane"
            ,
            "rightAnswer":"It is efficient"
            
        },
        {
            "id" : "9",

            "question" : "How do I view other people's opinions about me?",
            "leftAnswer":"I will change something about myself to fit in"
            ,
            "rightAnswer":"I don't care about what others think about me"
            
        },
        {
            "id" : "10",

            "question" : "How do I view physical appearances?",
            "leftAnswer":"Physical appearance is important to me"
            ,
            "rightAnswer":"Inside is what matters most"
            
        },
        {
            "id" : "11",

            "question" : "Who would I rather surround myself with?",
            "leftAnswer": "Simple individuals"
            ,
            "rightAnswer":"Complex individuals"
            
        },
        {
            "id" : "12",

            "question" : "How do I handle peer pressure?",
            "leftAnswer": "If all my friends were doing it, I would do it"
            ,
            "rightAnswer":"If I feel strongly about something, I wont let others influence me"
            
        },
        {
            "id" : "13",

            "question" : "How prevalent is death in my life?",
            "leftAnswer":"I've had people close to me die"
            ,
            "rightAnswer":"I have not experienced death"
            
        },
        {
            "id" : "14",

            "question" : "Would I help my best friend get away with murder?",
            "leftAnswer":"I would ask no questions and help them"
            ,
            "rightAnswer":"I would turn them in"
            
        }
    
        
    ]
}


